

#### **SUMMURY**

Innovative Web Developer with 3 years of experience in website design and coding. Demonstrated talent for front and back-end web development to optimize online presence. Seasoned expert in languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, php, mySql.

#### **CONTACT**

PHONE:

+216 50 870 256

LINKEDIN:

www.linkedin.com/in/maamoun-grissa

PORTFOLIO:

maamoun-grissa.netlify.app

E-MAIL:

grissa.maamoun@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

HTML / CSS / JavaScript / PHP / MySql jQuery / AlpineJS / Tailwindcss VueJS / ReactJs / AngularJs ReactNative / ionic-framework Laravel / Livewire Wordpress / opencart / joomla Foxpro / vb.net / c++

#### **LANGUAGES**

Arabic 0000

French OOOO

English 0000

Russian 0000

# MAAMOUN GRISSA

### Web Developer

#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

## Full Stack Web Developer Freelancer, Internet ( Remote )

2021 - Current

Development of websites, web and mobile applications:

- E-commerce plateforms using opencart cms & VueJS.
- Catalog & Portfolio websites using Wordpress cms & VueJS.
- Web & Mobile app using React JS & React Native + Api: Laravel 8 & Livewire 2 & Tailwindcss & Alpine Js.

#### Full Stack Web Developer Flegrei, Moscow, Russia

2019 - 2021

Development of websites, web and mobile applications:

- E-commerce plateforms using opencart cms.
- Catalog websites using Wordpress cms.
- Mobile app using lonic-framework & Angular Js + Api: Laravel 7.

#### Full Stack Web Developer Kvantum, Moscow, Russia ( Remote )

2019 - 2021

Development of websites, web and mobile applications:

- Catalog websites using joomla cms.
- Development of web application using Laravel 7.

#### System Administrator Hotel LTI El Ksar, Sousse, Tunisia

2013 - 2018

Management and maintenance of computers equipments, local networks, wifi networks, telephony, surveillance cameras, ERP system and audiovisual Manager.

#### Software Developer

Tunisian Compny of Equipments, Tunis, Tunisia

2011 - 2012

Development of ERP system of the company using FoxPro.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Higher institute of technological studies, Sousse, Tunisia

July 2011

Applied license in multimedia and web development

#### Higher institute of technological studies, Sousse, Tunisia

July 2010

Cisco certificate: home & small business networking